you
wei, wei
Can you hear
打个一
dees
I can hear it.
How is the sound?
I will turn down the volume.
Let's discuss it.
I can hear it.
Thank you.
There is a QR code on the list.
I will take it away.
Please remember to pull the QR code.
Let's talk for a few minutes.
There are QR codes on the list.
QR codes on the list.
Recently,
I received a lot of friends.
Not many friends.
One-on-one information.
I found that
sometimes,
although the situation is different,
the age is different,
the profession is different,
but the problem is
that life is the key turning point.
Because China
has been developing
from the economic development
to the slow-moving period.
Many people
in the way of life
and in the form of consciousness
don't adapt
to the new one.
So they face the problem of turning.
After I talked to them,
I gave them some suggestions.
What I want to tell you is that
life may be very long.
For decades,
life is the key.
But the real key
is the few steps.
The real key
When I was young,
I went to college
and got married.
After I got married,
I worked for several times.
For example, when I was 30 or 40,
I changed my job.
I couldn't go abroad.
I had to choose
because
it affected a lot of people.
Many people
don't have
a person
to talk to.
Because you have to make
these decisions.
You have to
know
about the situation.
The world you know
is as real as possible.
Or as real as possible.
Don't go too far.
It is also life.
What is life?
It is also a choice.
Sometimes you make the right choice.
Your choice is your life.
Your personality is your life.
When we came all the way,
a lot of older brothers
came.
A lot of older brothers' guidance.
His understanding of the situation.
Especially, he is a person who comes.
He is a person who comes to talk to you.
And his level of sleep is higher than yours.
The situation of experience is almost the same.
When we were young,
the things we experienced
in those older brothers
seemed to be very simple.
I may be older now.
I have experienced a lot of things.
In fact,
besides a friend,
I can't give him a better choice.
I can only give him
a better choice.
I can't give him a better choice.
I can only give him a better choice.
But sometimes,
in the situation,
you can't see clearly.
So,
you can talk to them.
don't tweet
or send a message.
You should go to the Patreon.
There is a product.
You should go there.
You should go there and buy the product.
Then, you should ask me for some time.
Then,
I will call you in advance.
Send me the message in advance.
If you don't feel at ease,
you don't need to tell me clearly.
Of course, I will keep it for you.
In this case,
you can come here one-on-one.
Shudan, you have to wait.
Shudan
has been busy recently.
In Japan,
it's not just about agriculture.
It's about Yuan Dan.
So, there are many things.
Can you hear me?
In the middle,
if others are against the question,
I will challenge you.
If you only listen to your live broadcast,
or if you have any questions,
I suggest you to leave.
Or refresh your mind.
If it's just your personal question,
if others don't respond,
it's your personal question.
Then, you should leave.
Or, the worst case is to restart.
This is so big.
It's all public information.
And now,
there are a lot of people who copy me.
They don't know who is the original person.
There are a lot of people who copy me
on Twitter today.
After copying,
they know it's me.
Some people want to help,
but don't reply.
Let me tell you.
A lot of people
copy me on Twitter.
Sometimes,
they can only copy a few people.
If the owner doesn't reply,
you can just leave.
Usually, I tell him,
he must reply within two days.
If he doesn't reply within two days,
you can remind him.
Because a lot of people
respond to him.
So, you can remind him.
Thank you.
Like this video.
If you want to add a group,
send your message to him.
Don't send it to him.
This process,
I think
I can reply
to most of the netizens.
Some netizens
wait for him to reply.
Think about it.
A lot of people contact him.
Of course,
this is a kind of exchange.
Contact anyone,
friends, colleagues,
or even leaders.
You have to think about it.
Don't ask for a group.
If you ask for a group,
send your message to him.
The worst part is to send your message to him.
I am also afraid
that others might send me a message.
Or send a message.
If you send a message,
I won't reply.
I can't listen to your long message.
If you send a message,
I won't reply.
I am sorry.
I have no time to listen.
Send a message to him.
You can contact him later.
Remember,
don't send a message.
Say hello directly.
Second, don't send a message.
You can read the text anytime.
Sometimes it is painful to listen to a message.
Everyone,
find someone to take a photo
on our YouTube platform.
If it is not convenient for you to take a photo,
you can take a photo.
Both platforms are different,
but both are the same.
In today's video,
I will be on both platforms
on YouTube.
You can watch the general live stream
Other content,
there are some drawbacks
but there are advantages.
It is better to send a long message.
I will send some messages.
Some messages are not convenient for me to send to the hotel.
There are some drawbacks
but there are some drawbacks.
It is more expensive than YouTube.
So it will be a little more expensive.
I have been taken away by the platform.
Let's start.
The status of the family
is not high.
It is mainly because of the small gold treasury.
Why do you talk about the provincial secretary?
In fact,
I just want to talk about these provincial secretary.
These people
can climb to the provincial secretary
in more than 10 billion.
From the 8,000 million staff members
to the 350 people in the group,
these people are all deaf.
Their vision has experienced all kinds of problems.
Let me talk about the provincial secretary.
It is not for everyone to say
that you are the provincial secretary
but for you.
These people are typical vision.
They are typical cases.
You can analyze these cases
through analysis.
You can analyze their vision
and their life situation.
You can get the rules on these vision.
If you are in the system
or are involved in work,
you can get the rules.
I am not the provincial secretary.
You are the president, the chief,
the county head, the mayor.
They are all the same.
Secondly,
you know
the future of these people
and how to analyze these people's vision.
You know
the starting point.
You can know
the future of these people.
You can find them
if you are the provincial secretary.
Don't think about the provincial secretary.
In fact, the provincial secretary
is the first time I met a provincial secretary
when I was in college.
I went to his house.
He was biting his teeth.
He was biting his teeth
and wanted to hold hands with me.
Then he said,
you will understand
the future of these people
in the future.
Thirdly,
why do you learn these things?
If you want to understand China,
I am not in the system.
I don't want to
work in a normal way.
For example,
I want to know the situation of China.
These groups
are all
you know Xi Jinping,
you don't know him well.
These provincial secretary are all small-scale Xi Jinping.
They are all small-scale leaders.
You can understand
the politics of China through him.
Every province
is different.
You can understand the ecology of each province.
You can do anything in China.
Even if you are a joke,
you can be a observer.
You have to know
who is in charge of this big situation.
For example, you are in Yunnan province.
If you don't know
his director,
you can't
understand him.
You can only see him
on the street.
How do you know?
Every province
is the provincial secretary.
Why do you talk about the provincial secretary?
It has nothing to do with you.
Everyone lives in
the system.
The provincial secretary is the best
in the system.
It is a big problem.
Let's talk about
southern and northwest.
What about
southwest?
Yunnan province.
The provincial secretary of Yunnan province
is Wang Ning.
He was born in 1961.
He is from Hunan province.
He was born in
Shenyang province.
Why do you have to study the system?
Because many systems
help each other.
Some places are very familiar.
For example,
Chen Xi got rid of
the
and he moved to
Sili province.
he was born in western
province.
He was born in women
Chen Xixi, although he is based on Lao Xiang's foundation,
but he doesn't come from Lao Xiang,
he doesn't really like the foundation of Lao Xiang.
But some people say Lao Xiang is very important in China.
So you have to study his habits,
know where he came from,
and the second thing is, you know his personality.
For example, Chen Ming'er, look, he is a mastermind.
A mastermind, many people say,
there is a line below Shaoxing,
Shaoxing is a mastermind, but it's not.
The mastermind is completely different from Shaoxing people.
The mastermind is more righteous.
The mastermind is a northeastern person from the south.
It's more bloody.
The mastermind is a gang member in Zhejiang.
The mastermind is very good at observing Zhejiang.
So when you see Chen Ming'er,
you know that the mastermind will also understand his path of life.
The mastermind is very close to him.
So Wang Jing's university is usually
talking about a university student.
He is a major or I forgot.
Anyway, his degree is average.
And then he is in the construction department for a long time.
He has been in the construction department for 83 years.
And then he has been doing it all the way to the front.
The progress is very slow, everyone knows.
Until 1999, he was still a private assistant engineer.
He was a deputy secretary.
In 2002, he went to Xinjiang to hang out with the manager.
The manager of Xinjiang Construction Department is hanging out with the manager.
Think about it, he went to Xinjiang for his progress.
Xinjiang is also very backward now.
It's hard to hang out.
And it's so far away from home.
He went to Urumqi.
Maybe it's far away from the East China Sea.
So he can't do anything about his progress.
Then he went to Xinjiang to hang out with the manager.
Then in 2005, he was promoted to the deputy director of the construction department.
The mastermind is a private secretary.
In 2008, he became a private secretary.
When you look at him as a private secretary,
you know that he has entered the core position.
Why did he get promoted?
Because in 2001, the director of the construction department was changed to Wang Guangtao.
Wang Guangtao has been the director of the construction department for 08 years.
So Wang Ning's main foundation in the construction department is Wang Guangtao's hands.
Wang Guangtao went to hang out with the manager for 05 years in 2002.
He was also the director of the nuclear power plant.
He was also the director of the director of the construction department.
Then he became a private secretary.
This is all under Wang Guangtao's control.
Wang Guangtao, you all know that he used to hang out with the construction department all the time.
He used to be the director of the nuclear power plant.
Then he was the deputy director of the construction department in Beijing.
He is also an old man in the construction field.
Then in 2013, Wang Ning became the deputy director of the construction department.
Who was the deputy director at that time?
It was Jiang Weixin, a younger brother of Zeng Peiyan.
He was originally promoted to the vice director of the nuclear power plant.
In 2013, he became the deputy director of the construction department.
At that time, he was actually always in the construction department.
You see, from 1983 to 2013,
it was nearly 30 years ago.
Then this is all part of the construction department of the nuclear power plant.
In general, the nuclear power plant has been developing in a department like this.
Then he became the deputy director and basically came to an end.
But when he was 15, he tried to change.
He became the deputy director of the construction department in 2015.
He became a secretary in Fuzhou in 2017.
He became the deputy director of Fuzhou in 2020.
He was in Yunnan Street in 2011.
His life, you see, the second most important part of his life,
was in Fuzhou.
He stayed for about six years from 2015 to 2015.
He was the deputy director of Fuzhou and the deputy director of Fuzhou.
During this time, everyone knows that Fuzhou has a lot of communication channels with Xi Jinping,
including his old leader, including the former Nile expert.
including the previous secretary of Fuzhou,
the two old men can recommend Ganbo.
You have communicated with him, including Chen Xi and Cai Qi.
Especially Chen Xi has a lot of contact with Fuzhou.
Because he is the deputy director of Fuzhou,
he has received this Fujian thing.
There must be a lot of contact with Chen Xi.
So in the middle of this, he basically communicated with Xi's channel.
So in the 21st year, he received this Yunnan secretary.
But Wang Ning, in Yunnan,
because in Yunnan, everyone knows that there are a lot of things going on.
Recently, Li Ji Heng, everyone is going to be in trouble again.
So the secretary of Yunnan has very few contacts.
Li Ji Heng is in trouble.
Because I uploaded a video of Li Ji Heng a few days ago.
Everyone take a look.
Li Ji Heng is actually quite busy.
When he was in Guangxi, he did a lot of things.
And when he was in Yunnan, he also suffered a lot of things.
But after Wang Ning came up,
the situation in Yunnan was probably ruined.
The secretary of Yunnan, the secretary of Yunnan,
didn't have a few contacts.
Chen Hao might have been involved this time.
Because he caught a key businessman.
At the same time, Li Ji Heng also told Chen Hao.
But the people on Chen Hao are still here.
So Chen Hao doesn't know what to do.
But Wang Ning is probably in trouble.
Thank you, Mr. Xue.
After he was in trouble, he did things.
He didn't have any power to do anything.
That's how the ministry of justice came out.
So his influence in Yunnan is the same.
Anyway, Wang Ning is almost there.
This is a ministry of justice.
But what's strange is that he has changed.
It's very successful to change.
Second, look at his early experience.
You see, he has been suffering for so many years.
So don't worry.
He solved the problem and spent 13 years.
He spent 16 years.
Second, let's talk about Guizhou's Xu Lin.
Xu Lin was in June of 1963.
He graduated from Shanghai, Nanjiang.
He graduated from the University of Shanghai.
Xu Lin's professionalism is not high.
When he graduated from the University of Shanghai in 1982,
he was a middle school teacher.
He was the secretary of the middle school committee.
Because everyone knows that in the county,
he often went to the middle school to elect the secretary of the committee.
So he became the secretary of the committee.
He became the secretary of the village committee.
Nanjiang was an old county under Shanghai.
He was later sick.
So he became the secretary of the county committee of Nanjiang.
I guess this kid can write.
Then in 1992, he became the deputy president.
In 1995, he became the secretary of the family district.
He became the deputy president.
In the middle, he went to Rikaze, Tibet.
This is called Yuanzang.
In 1997, he became the general manager of the Shanghai Agricultural Company.
Then he was promoted to the chairman.
The agricultural company group knew that it was under the Shanghai Agricultural Committee.
So in this stage,
the main topic is Meng Jianzhu.
Because he has been in this county.
He has been in the agricultural system of the agricultural company.
At that time, the Shanghai Agricultural Committee was mainly under Meng Jianzhu's control.
Then Meng Jianzhu became the deputy president of the agricultural company.
Then in 2003, Xu Lin became the director of the Civil Affairs Bureau.
We all know that about 2001, Meng Jianzhu left.
Because who was he with?
With Huang Jue or Chen Liangyu?
With Huang Jue, it should be the secretary of the county committee of Shanghai.
He arranged for him to go to Jiangxi.
At this time, it was with Xu Lin.
There was no boss in Shanghai.
He broke his leg.
He broke his leg, but he was also a regular.
So you see, after 2001, Xu Lin has always changed.
Because Chen Liangyu and Huang Jue didn't like Meng Jianzhu.
So he has always been changed.
So he became the director of the Civil Affairs Bureau in 2003.
In 2007,
you see, he has been in the government for so many years.
He only appointed a farm owner.
So you see, when he was in the government of Chen Liangyu,
Xu Lin was more changeable.
But in February 2007, he was still the farm owner.
But at this time, you know,
in March 2007, a new secretary came to Shanghai.
Chen Liangyu was in trouble.
A secretary named Xi Jinping came to Shanghai.
So in May, the Shanghai committee was elected.
The Standing Committee of the Shanghai Committee.
At that time, when Xi Jinping introduced him,
did you have any impression?
I don't know.
It's said that this is our youngest Standing Committee.
In addition, he said that he supported Xi Zao.
When Xi Jinping introduced him, he said these two words.
So you see, Xu Lin has a direct relationship with Xi Jinping.
Although it's very short, about half a year.
The second one is that Xi Jinping was the one who solved it.
Then why did Xi Jinping solve it?
Because his level is just enough.
In addition, he must have been with Chen Liangyu.
You don't have to worry about him, you don't have to worry about him.
You don't have to worry about a person.
It's not easy for you to worry about a person.
As a result, you find that this is Chen Liangyu.
Who else can get rid of him?
So after this, he entered the Standing Committee of the Shanghai Committee.
After that, he became a general secretary.
He became the head of the Standing Committee of the Shanghai Committee.
He became the head of the Standing Committee of the Shanghai Committee in 2013.
In 2015, he became the vice-chairman of the Central Committee of the Shanghai Committee.
Why did he fall at this time?
Because Xi Jinping used human rights from 2015 to 2016.
Before that, Xi Jinping was actually a user.
He was very careful.
You observe Xi Jinping's user.
You will find that he used a wave of people in 2013.
This is his most iron and Li Qiang Chenmier's wave.
In 2014, Huang Kunming fell to the Central Committee.
Then Cai Qi fell to the National Security Office.
This wave was basically his most ironed wave in 2015.
He used a wave in 2016 and 2017.
This is the second circle of his fellow members.
Xu Lin belongs to this second circle.
But he didn't solve the Ministry of Justice for him.
In June 2016, he became the head of the Wang Xinbans.
He was the main leader of the Wang Xinbans.
You know that Lu Wei, the vice-chairman of the New York Times,
is the general secretary of the Wenjia Bao brand.
He was the leader of the Wang Xinbans,
the leader of the Wu Xinbans,
and Lu Wei.
In the early years of Xi Jinping,
he also used Lu Wei to be his prime minister.
For example, he went to the bun shop,
to eat buns,
to the Xima,
and to the Xima,
and Lu Wei was the prime minister.
So you see,
Xi Jinping's image was very clear.
But Lu Wei,
this guy,
he was very loyal to the surface,
but he did that little thing by himself.
Later,
he was also used in the middle of Xuling.
It was said that Lu Wei and Xi Jinping
fought very fiercely against Xuling.
Lu Wei used a group of security guards
to defend Xuling.
At first,
Lu Wei,
you see,
Xi Jinping's departure
was following Lu Wei.
Hei Ping, right?
That's your business.
Don't worry, everyone.
Let's have a try.
The system is not very good.
Because I don't understand the system.
We are all equal in front of the system.
Including the payment problem,
your money is paid to the platform.
You have to find the platform to speed up,
including using the system.
I'm not very clear.
You try it yourself, okay?
So,
there was a fight between Lu Wei and Xuling.
Xuling helped Xi Jinping
to get rid of some of the material.
That's how Lu Wei got rid of it.
So, you can see that Lu Wei's
dealings
were written very fiercely.
Almost all of the security guards
were the most malicious ones.
The boss hated him a lot.
He said,
I trust you.
I will take you to see Jack Boga.
I will take you to the kitchen.
You will be involved in these things.
You will have a very rich life.
Lu Wei got rid of it.
Lu Wei is very nice to Xiao Yan.
So, he was very harsh to him.
You should check his dealings.
He was very harsh to him.
He said,
this person is really his mother.
You should be the most malicious one.
So, after Xuling became the leader of the Internet.
He knew that the power of the Internet
was the biggest power in the Central Committee.
Originally, the Internet was an edge.
But because the Internet is too big now.
These Internet companies
basically can control it.
Everyone knows how big their power is.
Including people like Teng Xun,
who is the leader of the Internet.
Everyone knows that
they have the power to control the whole network.
So, everyone knows his power.
It is almost the biggest power in the Central Committee.
It can be said that
the whole department of the Internet
is the biggest power in the whole network.
Don't look at him as a popular person.
Think about it.
If he managed the Weibo a little better
or just wanted to go crazy
He was arrested for a few days, and a long time later, he was arrested for a few days.
So, it's okay, everyone.
It's not easy for me to do a live broadcast in the middle of the night.
18 years later, Xu Lin was the director of the National News Agency.
After the National News Agency, he was actually in charge of the Internet before the National News Agency.
Later, these two institutions were separated.
The National News Agency was actually in charge of the Internet before the National News Agency.
At the age of 22, he was arrested for a long time.
In the middle of the night, Xu Lin was influenced by Sun Lijun and Meng Jianzhu's incident.
The position of Xu Lin was very...
He was turned around on a platform.
In fact, he was completely okay with the deputy director of the Central News Agency.
His relationship with Xi, and his propaganda experience,
he was completely okay with the deputy director of the Central News Agency.
Or, at this time, he must have been a bit lost.
Thank you, Tang Tang.
By the year 22, he officially received the secretary of Guizhou.
The whole attempt was repeated.
Xu Lin's biggest point of view is his direct relationship with Xi Jinping.
Let's take a look at Sichuan.
Sichuan is Wang Xiaohui's current secretary.
In August of 62nd, he was an urgent person.
He was a senior member of the Supreme Court.
He is similar to Wang Ning.
He has also been in the department of graduation.
After graduation in 1986, he entered the Central News Agency.
He has been in the Central News Agency for 36 years.
So, let's take a look at Wang Ning.
They are all part of the department.
He is a professional director.
After he entered the Central News Agency, he was in the propaganda agency.
He went to the political, legal and research department.
He went to the fishing and theory department.
He became the deputy director.
In 2009, he became the deputy director.
In 2010, he became the spokesman.
Thank you, Ma Wen.
Thank you.
It's all my heart.
Now that the two of them are here.
In 2014, he was in the propaganda agency for 6 months.
It is still the deputy director of the Central News Agency.
He just became a deputy director of the media agency.
He didn't go to the propaganda agency to be the deputy director.
In the second month of 2017, he became deputy director of the newspaper agency.
At that time, he was in the Ministry of Justice.
He also became the deputy director of the media agency.
He still didn't leave the media agency.
This is his key point.
In January 2018, when he became the deputy director of Zheng Yan City for less than a year,
he returned to the Central Propaganda Department and became the deputy director of the Civil Defense Department.
At that time, he was still the deputy director of Zheng Yan City until the summer of 2018.
Then this middle-aged director took over the movie theater.
So everyone found that because Zheng Yan City was the deputy director,
he must have treated Wang Huning.
But everyone found that he was the deputy director of Zheng Yan City.
The first stage was to supervise.
The second stage was to supervise the deputy director of Zheng Yan City.
He only communicated with Wang Huning for less than a year.
By April 2022, he went to Sichuan to be a secretary.
So many people say that Wang Yao Hui is Wang Huning's person.
In fact, it's wrong.
Of course, the relationship on this face will work.
But he is not Wang Huning's person.
But who is he?
First of all, he has been in the Central Propaganda Department for so long.
Especially in 2009, he solved the deputy director.
So he and Liu Yunshan's relationship should be very strong.
Of course, Li Changchun will also recognize him.
This can't be avoided.
In addition, I will tell you that no one has ever said this on the Internet.
Wang Yao Hui has long been relying on Xi Jinping.
When he was in the Central Propaganda Department,
at least from that time, he knew Xi Jinping.
Then he established a relatively good relationship with Xi Jinping.
Everyone knows that when Xi Jinping started his presidency,
he wanted to make his politics a little better.
In the last episode, I said that he used some new Chinese companies,
and even used some Yan'an TV media to create his own brand image.
Of course, some media like Yang Mei,
like Xinhua News Agency and People's Daily,
he is the leader of the Central Propaganda Department.
Like the Daily newspaper and the TV station in the province,
the TV station was arranged by a former secretary of his own.
He was the head of the office,
because he was in poor health,
so he specially arranged a TV station for him
to promote his image of the province.
Yan'an TV used to promote his image of the public's love for him.
So at that time, he accepted a lot of media interviews.
At that time, other than knowing him,
for example, I have told you about the Zhang of the Central Propaganda Department,
the little old man of Xi Jinping, Zhang Jianchun.
And he had some friends in every department.
The Deputy Minister of the Central Propaganda Department,
and later the former Secretary of the State of Sichuan,
what's his name? Wang.
That was also his old friend.
Like the Daily newspaper, Wang Chen,
he was a good friend of Yan'an TV.
And he had a good friend in the Central Propaganda Department.
Wang Xiaohui was very close to him since then.
So everyone knew him.
So Wang Xiaohui was very early to rely on his team.
So why?
So at that time, in 2014,
he sent him to be the Deputy Minister of the Central Propaganda Department.
In 2017, he accepted the Deputy Minister of the Central Propaganda Department.
Then he sent him back to be the Deputy Minister of the Central Propaganda Department.
At the time, Wang Xiaohui was in the Central Propaganda Department.
Everyone knows that when Huang Kunming was in Zhejiang,
it was around 2010,
not 2010, but earlier, around 2007,
Huang Kunming was the deputy minister of Zhejiang.
He was interested in the policy of the Central Propaganda Department.
He also had to run away.
So at that time, Huang Kunming was looking for Wang Xiaohui.
But at that time, Huang Kunming had been in the Central Propaganda Department as the deputy minister.
So he transferred Wang Xiaohui to be the deputy director of the factory.
Because Huang Kunming is a foreign minister.
The Central Committee is such a big mechanism.
You are the deputy director.
You have never done it before. You can't win.
You can't win.
Or you have a good deputy director.
You will do a lot of things.
So of course, Huang Kunming likes to use Wang Xiaohui who has a relationship with himself.
So there will be a lot of trouble in the future.
But let me tell you that Wang Huening doesn't take people.
Except for Lin Shangli of the People's University.
Including the later director, Jiang Jingquan.
Jiang Jingquan has a good relationship with him on the surface.
But later on, he had a long way to go.
He had a long way to go.
So why can Wang Huening not fall?
He and Zhao Leji are one way.
I don't have the right to do anything.
I don't have my own style.
You don't have any threats to you.
I don't recommend myself.
Except for the people who need to work.
Even the deputy director of the factory is your recommendation.
I am all your people.
Do you trust me?
So Wang Huening, including Zhao Leji,
his history studies are very thorough.
His study is so thorough that he got these things.
So he followed his people.
But he got his own life.
He didn't have a lot of power when I was in power.
He didn't have so many people.
But my power is longer.
So why can't they be connected to the factory in the 20th century?
This is almost the same as his style.
If Wang Qishan could understand this,
he wouldn't have the back.
Right?
Let's talk about Gan Su.
Let's talk about Xi Bei.
Xi Bei, let me see.
Let's talk about the two or three of them.
Gan Su is Hu Changsheng.
Hu Changsheng was a Jiangxi student in December of 1963.
He was a student in Chengdu Geography Academy.
Hu Changsheng was a student leader who was a student with us.
When he graduated, he stayed in Chengdu Geography Academy.
He was not a teacher.
He was a group secretary.
He was a party secretary.
Then he transferred to Chengdu Geography Academy as deputy director.
He was a county secretary in 2002.
During this time, he had a big characteristic.
Look at his resume.
He didn't have a doctor in Sichuan.
He went to Shanda to study history.
Many people were surprised.
Why?
Because his teacher went back to Shanda after he graduated from Sichuan University.
So he went to Shanda with his teacher to study a doctor.
His research subject is Taoism.
Hu Changsheng is a Taoist expert.
Our great leader also likes Taoism.
He is also very interested in this religion.
So Hu Changsheng's doctor thesis is about Taoism.
In 2004, he transferred to Ya'an.
He was a group secretary and then became a county secretary.
In 2006, he went to Sui Ning as deputy director.
The first lady in Hu Changsheng's life was Zhang Xuezhong.
During this time,
Hu Changsheng went to Sui Ning as deputy director in Ya'an.
During this time, he was the leader of Zhang Xuezhong.
These two key steps were to be the deputy director.
These two steps were difficult.
At the time, he was called Zhang Xuezhong.
Zhang Xuezhong, do you know who he is?
He was a work in Gansu.
He was the secretary of Hu Changsheng.
Later, he was the deputy director in Tibet.
Hu Jintao was a group secretary.
He was very close to Hu.
So Zhang Xuezhong treated him very well.
Zhang Xuezhong later retired.
Then Liu Qibao was the director of Ganzizhou.
In 2006, Hu Changsheng was the deputy director.
In 2012, he was the secretary of Ganzizhou.
He was the deputy director for six years.
This time was long.
The middle part was broken.
The scary thing about Liu Qibao is that he didn't treat him well.
That's what he said.
What happened in Ganzizhou?
In Ganzizhou, when he arrived in 2015,
he was transferred to Qinghai as deputy director.
In the middle,
everyone knew that from the jump,
the deputy director was not the deputy director.
Because he is now the deputy director of Ganzizhou.
But at that time, he was not in the scene.
There was a Qiyu in the middle.
There must be Qiyu.
He knew a high person.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have come.
But his secretary of Ganzizhou,
like Liu Qibao,
wouldn't recommend him.
Liu Qibao is also a person who doesn't stick to the pot.
Why did he come up with Qiyu?
On November 24, 2014,
there was a Kanding line below Ganzizhou.
There was a Kanding earthquake at level 6.3.
Kanding was the place where the Kanding song was played.
After the Kanding earthquake,
because the level 6.3 was not small in China at that time.
It was very close to Wenchuan in 2008.
It was Sichuan.
So the subsequent disaster,
including the Central Committee,
caused a lot of trouble for Ganzi.
Xi Jinping especially called.
The leader should have been there.
So he performed better in this process.
So he also knew some of the central leaders.
So imagine that in 2014,
there was an earthquake at the end of November.
He had to be in jail for three months.
Then on June 2nd,
he went to Qinghai to be the head of the organization.
Why did your program last for two or three months?
In this case, he had just been in jail.
He was immediately arrested.
That's how small it was.
In the head of the organization in Qinghai,
he was transferred to Fujian in 2017.
So the two head of the organization
had a relationship with Chen Xi at that time.
Then he was in Fujian and Chen Xi's camp.
Then in 2019, he went to Xiamen to be the secretary.
He knew who Xiamen was.
He was He Lifeng, the head of the organization in Xiamen.
Then the chief secretary had a cousin who had been in Xiamen.
So Xiamen was also a political highland.
So he had a formal relationship with Xiamen.
In this way, you can see that he had Chen Xi.
The head of the organization was very considerate of him.
Then there was He Lifeng,
the first relative of our Uyghur leader.
And he was very considerate of him.
So the two people kept pushing.
In the 21st year, he took the governor of Henglongjiang.
In the 22nd year, he took the secretary of Gansu.
That's the case.
But he did a good job in Xiamen.
He had a lot of business with Xiamen.
He must have solved the problem in Xiamen.
He only solved a part of it.
Let's take a look at Wu Xiaojun, who was killed.
Wu Xiaojun is 66 years old.
He is now a relatively young secretary.
Then he graduated from the University of Jiangxi.
He has been in Jiangxi.
His life has been in Jiangxi for a long time.
At first, he graduated from the Department of Economic Information.
The Department of Economic Information was not the Department of Economic Information.
He was then taken to the Ministry of Rural Affairs.
It was called the Ministry of Public Affairs under the Ministry of Rural Affairs.
After that, he officially went to the Ministry of Rural Affairs.
After that, in 1994, he was promoted by Huang Zhiquan.
Later, he became the governor of the province of Jiangxi.
At that time, he was deputy secretary.
Huang Zhiquan was the deputy secretary of the office of Jiangxi.
Then he was promoted by the deputy secretary of the province of Jiangxi.
So he was taken from the system of Rural Affairs.
When his secretary was Wu Xiaojun,
he looked quite similar.
Everyone found out that the leader chose the secretary.
The general people chose him.
He was similar to him.
The leader was a little boy.
He chose a little boy.
But he chose a big brother.
So they were both mysterious.
It may be that after the two people saw the leader for a long time,
they deliberately went to that room to imitate him.
So when everyone saw,
a lot of the secretary and the leader were mysterious.
So they were both mysterious.
So he followed Wu Xiaojun and Huang Zhiquan all the time.
From the deputy chief of the provincial government office,
to the deputy chief of the provincial government office.
Then Huang Zhiquan withdrew.
Then he went to Huang Zhiquan.
Who is Huang Zhiquan's friend?
Huang Zhiquan is from Zhejiang.
He graduated from Zhejiang Agricultural University.
He graduated from two people.
One is Huang Zhiquan and the other is Li Qiang.
He is our current president.
After Huang Zhiquan withdrew,
Wu Xiaojun家ー
transferred from the provincial government office till its να sleepy,
becoming deputy director of the provincial government office,
and then he went to be deputy director, director of the provincial government office.
Then he деньги acting as a deputy director for the attempting job in the provincial administration office under 13 years.
Then he Nordic ops was made.
Then it went on for every seven years.
Then who was the secondướ of his life?
Which is Lu Xingshe.
After him became Mo Xi's secretarymit,
Lu Xingshe in his hands solved the problem.
and transferred him to the provincial committee as the core director,
including Vice President Lu Xingsheng, who was also very considerate of him.
Thank you, Mr. Zhu Lieliu.
So this Lu Xingsheng is the second most noble person in his life.
In 2017, he became Vice President,
General Vice President, and then became the secretary of Nanchang for a year.
Then he transferred to Qinghai as the secretary.
Then he received the administration of Qinghai and the secretary of Qinghai.
In the middle of this,
I don't know if he grew up looking for Li Qiang,
but when he was in Jiangxi,
he and the great brother-in-law of our Wudang University
had a great time.
You all know that Dejiakui entrusted to Jiangxi a system frame.
At that time, the connection to this system frame was Wu Xiaoyun.
Because he was in charge of the construction and development.
These were all led by Vice President Lu and Nanchang.
So he solved a lot of problems for this.
So this was the key reason for him to be the secretary of the provincial committee.
But Qinghai is a small secretary.
He must also go abroad.
If he develops well, he will definitely have to make a bigger deal.
That is to say, with the previous Chen Gang and these people,
Xin Changxing, these are almost the same way.
Then we have a little time.
Let's briefly talk about Wang Junzheng.
Wang Junzheng is now a secretary of Tibet.
The secretary of Tibet is a man from Shandong in 1963.
He graduated from Shandong University.
He is also good at studying.
Many people say that Wang Junzheng is the one.
He is from Penglin.
One says Shandong is his hometown.
This is wrong.
It's not that he was born in Shandong, he was born in Shandongbao.
He was born in Shandongbao.
Wang Junzheng's life journey is like this.
He is a little similar to Wu Xiaoyun.
He was also a secretary.
In 1988, he entered the former labor office as a secretary.
He has been following this Lin Hu'an.
Lin Hu'an, you know, started with the labor office.
Later, Lin Hu'an arrived in Yunnan.
When he was the governor, he also followed Lin Hu'an.
Before Lin Hu'an left, he arranged him to be a secretary of Kunming's Guandu.
Then he was a long-time secretary.
But after this, everyone knows that Li Ting, Li Jiating,
was the governor.
Lin Hu'an was transferred to the provincial bureau.
He was transferred to the provincial bureau and was affected.
But later, Bai Enpui took over this Lin Hu'an.
But Bai Enpui is also okay with him.
He got him from the deputy secretary of Kunming's organization.
Then he got the deputy director of Yunnan high school.
Finally, he went to Li Jiang in 2007.
Then he took over the secretary in 2009.
Everyone knows that during this period,
he was in Bai Enpui's hands to complete this promotion.
Everyone in Li Jiang knows this is a good place.
This kind of scenery is good.
Generally, it's a business.
Why?
Because after the leadership went to China,
you can give the leadership a lot of research.
The leadership is more fun.
You can get along with him.
You see, when Li Jiang was alive,
like Jia Qinglin's son-in-law went to that place to buy land.
Then a lot of people went there to do projects.
You have the opportunity to let the leadership family come and play.
You can take over.
The leadership will come to the end of the year.
There are a lot of contact points with the leadership.
You have a lot of benefits.
You can beat it.
You see, the later secretary of Li Jiang.
What is that called?
He became the head of the National School of Education.
That kid is also a talent.
He used Li Jiang's reception screen to make it good for everyone.
Li Zhan's daughter, you see,
went to the National School of Education.
She used Yunnan's name.
So she, you see,
she jumped from Yunnan to Li Jiang's secretary
directly to the National School of Education.
She jumped very high.
But she was also very attractive.
She voted for Chang'an, that kid.
She voted for a girl from the foreign Tibetan organization.
Then she was discovered by the state.
Then she reported it to him.
Then everyone knew that Cui Mao Hu.
You see his resignation.
He went up.
You think it's not clear.
It's not clear when you come down.
You became such a big official.
You still go to this show.
You say you this.
This is Li Jiang.
He went to Li Jiang's secretary.
Then in 2012, he crossed the province.
He went to Hubei.
He became the deputy governor.
And then he became the secretary of Xiangyang.
I used to write a story about Xiangyang.
It's called Xiangyang Pai.
Xiangyang is the place where Xi Jinping's ancestral grave is.
So Xi Jinping often went to the exam.
So Xiangyang Pai was very powerful.
He set up several political secretaries.
In the first quarter of the country, he was the only one.
Even the so-called Fu Ping and Yan'an were not as powerful as he was.
So he was the one who gave Xi Jia and Xi Jinping a relationship.
He went to Xiangyang's secretary.
So he later transferred to Changchun's secretary.
He went to Xinjiang's political party secretary.
Then he went to Xinjiang's military group.
He knew that the military group was China's unit.
He was a political party secretary.
You can understand him as a province of China.
Then he led the military group as a secretary from the military group.
Because he studied in Xinjiang for advanced experience.
So he transferred him to the advanced unit.
He called the number.
He learned how to suppress the people from Chenyuan.
And then he transferred him to Tibet as a secretary.
Overall, this is Wang Jingzheng.
There should be some provinces in the northwest.
Let's talk about it next time.
Today is the same day.
OK, you can ask questions.
And then Patron,
The problem is that you may have your own network.
Maybe the VPN you use is caused by the network.
Because most of what Patron is doing is fine.
There are a few black screen teachers.
Or what is the teacher?
One of them is you try the network.
You try to see your network or your VPN.
Why is Dengzhou the most direct home for Xi Jinping?
Because Xi Jinping's ancestors are like this.
The first thing is that in fact, there is a saying.
It is Xiangyang.
Xiangyang moved to Jiangxi.
From Jiangxi to Dengzhou.
From Dengzhou to Fuping.
Why can't Dengzhou?
Because Xi Jinping is one of...
One is Xi Jinping.
At that time, the Henan province of Dengzhou.
It is Xi Jinping.
At that time, the Henan provincial secretary of Dengzhou was Lu Zhai-guo.
Lu Zhai-guo didn't like to make this kind of thing in Dengzhou then.
The second thing is that
Xi Jinping's family was also afraid of Dengzhou's,
Dengzhou had to do something so dirty.
Xi Jinping was worried.
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you.
He worried about this.
He was worried it would leave a scar on his opponent.
So they sent people to say that they don't want to play the new game.
And the whole level of Dengzhou itself is too low.
It's too poor, I've been to Dengzhou.
So Dengzhou didn't get up. This is very comprehensive.
Did you have the same training? I didn't hear about it.
This is the first time I've heard about it.
Xizhongxun is quite good at Dengzhou.
Welcome.
Xizhongxun.
Xizhongxun Group.
Xizhongxun, I have to write it down.
It's too complicated.
Where is Wang Jinzheng?
I don't know. It's not set yet.
Xizhongxun is also a small place.
Xizhongxun is a small place.
In addition, Wang Jinzheng is a little...
Now his strength is a little weak.
His strength is not as good as it used to be.
So something happened to Xizhongxun.
So I guess he doesn't have much contact with that person.
So I'm not very good at it.
Originally, Xizhongxun was the best to go back to Xinjiang.
But he didn't dare to go back to Xinjiang.
Su'er.
Su'er is Wu Qingwen.
Wu Qingwen was born in college, right?
He was a high school student.
He was born in college.
He was also a secretary in the early years.
Did he come to Xinjiang or did you like it?
I'd made five rounds of games with him.
I rose with Xixikey.
King Xun Xingya now gives very good feedback.
I think you didn't want to枪 suddenly.
Xixikey didn't get to the table last time because he couldn't move in.
So go with Yixikey if you don't want to.
It is very likely that Wang Xiaohong will be the second hand of the Central Committee.
Recently, there is a lot of power in the future.
Zhou Hongbo.
Zhou Hongbo used to be in Nanjing.
He used to play in Sanya.
We all know that Sanya is like Li Jiang.
People who used to stay in such a place.
A lot of leaders will go to Sanya, you know.
In these places, people in these places are not good at talking.
He Nan.
After I finished talking about these,
after I finished talking about this,
I will talk about it separately.
For example, He Nan.
Yun Nan.
I will talk about it separately.
Some people,
some people,
they will not say that he is alone.
Some people, he is two people.
Sometimes he is close to a few people.
Some people say that he is not the one who is kicked out.
He is not the person who is kicked out.
He is not the one who is kicked out.
He is not like that.
Everyone must understand.
The secretary of the Ninhu is his boyfriend.
I really don't know.
You are too close.
I will study it.
Later, I will go out to observe the same training.
Do you have any evidence that you said that Ninhu is his boyfriend?
You see what I am talking about.
I have tested it.
There are more accurate statements.
Xu Li Yi, Xu Li Yi.
The problem at that time,
even the general secretary was angry.
Because he was not the boss's direct subordinate.
He actually has nothing to do with the boss.
It's just that he is the subordinate of that person.
The boss didn't protect him.
The boss wanted to punish him.
Xu Li Yi, Xu Li Yi.
What about Cai Yingwen?
The wind.
The wind was the one in 2017.
The wind should have come out now.
The wind is coming out soon.
The wind has already come out.
In this way, the boss is a successful woman.
Will the Chinese economy fall down in the next five years?
I have said it before.
Everyone will suffer.
Do you know?
What is suffering?
It's just that you have a wound on your body.
It's a little bit broken.
It's not that the kind of broken tooth is not working.
It won't work.
The Chinese economy is too big.
There are a lot of feedback attacks.
Look, there are so many people out this year.
So he is in the same boat.
The same boat is a disaster.
It won't work at once.
It won't work.
So the CCP said it would collapse soon.
It will collapse soon.
It won't work at once.
But if you are a big historical figure,
you can't predict a big historical event.
That's possible.
Before, Zhou Hongbo was the secretary-in-chief of Ma Biao, right?
He should have someone else after Ma Biao.
Because Ma Biao didn't have anything to do with it.
What about Tong Daochi?
I still remember Tong Daochi.
But I forgot Tong Daochi.
He did a lot of things at the Chinese New Year's Day.
My friend was familiar with him.
He went to the mountains to see him.
He taught me.
I was abroad at that time.
Tong Daochi came out of the Chinese New Year's Day.
He knew this very well.
So he was in the Chinese New Year's Day.
He should have been the one who signed the contract.
The president of Ma Bihua, Chongqing,
that one of them,
should have been the one who signed the contract.
He came out of the Chinese New Year's Day.
Who was he?
He was the one who invested in the company.
He signed a group of people.
Then he caught Ma Bihua.
Later, he did one thing.
He went to other things.
He went to the mountains.
Yu Huemin was also from Ganzi.
Duan Yijun was also from Ganzi.
He signed the contract.
I see your position is very important.
More important is an international community.
Don't worry too much.
You will see more and more international communities
do the more important things.
That'sappearance.
About our lord's wise,
还是新的博弈了吧,啊,所以比较慢嘛。
组织系统最近比较混乱。
余惠文应该是李干杰的人。
玉惠文应该是李干杰的人。
你说环保系统,怎么办?
他在四川环保厅的时候应该跟这个李干杰搞上了。
现在就是陈锡李干杰在他掌握着中组部的中下层。
省委书记一年工资有多少?
几十万吧。
谢谢东,谢谢东的那个。
谢谢东的打赏,谢谢。
你就是衣食父母。
谭京啊,谭京是个另一句话。
大概姓怀也关于不错。
当时谭京同志在打电话指挥另一句话干事嘛。
谭京后来就差点被干掉了,因为国母很讨厌的。
我有次吃饭,我基本没认出来。
他就趴在那儿,过来敬酒。
敬到我边上,我发现,这个人,我说你看着你,
我说这么眼熟呢。
他就因为戴了个那个黑眼镜,
他头型也换了。
谭京的老公还是另一句话给介绍了。
夏林茂,有可夏林茂是蔡奇的人啊。
如果另外两家没有那个,蔡林茂也是备份啊。
海南明天讲,明天讲很难。
要走出通缩,自由靠站的人,有很多办法,
改福利制度也行啊,有很多办法。
青海的夏任政协主席,这个难不懂啊,
政协主席太难预测了,谁都能干,你去干也行。
王金正下一步,今生复国籍吗?
目前看他的竞争力弱一点,也不是不可能。
就是这个复国籍非很多嘛,
你像复主席什么的,
但是他现在资历稍微弱点,还得换个省是最好的。
刘兴泰,刘兴泰贪污啊,刘兴泰很霸道的,
没听说过刘兴泰的那些故事吗?
他在日照的时候就很霸道吧,
他能上去,就是在当地就搞了很多事,
欺负企业干啥的,
在海南又当政协委书记,
都是黑暗的部门。
胡玉婷啊,胡玉婷等着,等着我讲吧,
胡玉婷是谁的人来着,
他在这边靠着我。
马彪,马彪是这样,私交是好跟老大,
但是马彪不怎么推人。
马彪那个人也是比较谨慎的。
你想想还有谁啊?
广西现在就是那个科技厅长姓李的,
把他儿子搬进北大,那个是他的人,
还有那些人啊,你这一两个呢不算。
当过他的秘书长,有我没研究这个黄卫京,
当过他的秘书长,不一定是他推的,
有很多人就是跟着他解决了副部级之后,
解决副部级这个轻松一点。
咱俩说的推人不是一个概念,
泰国柬埔寨后期怎么发展,
打到那个谁呗,打到谁服呗,
打到那个谁服,打到那个洪森服器啊。
刘志军啊,刘志军是个能干啊,
没有他才就是对中国经济起到重大发展,
工程啊,民族工程啊,
然后能力特别强,没他根本干不,没有后边的事啊。
但是他说政治上犯错误了,
换大腿换错了,
所以被干掉了,
政治很复杂,
他把文也搞定了,江也搞定了,
他谁都没想到胡锦涛突然提示,
到现在谁都不知道胡锦涛怎么突然提示,
刘志军,
但是周级委抓刘志军挺有意思,
我是比较早,
可能是最早的几个知道刘志军要被抓的人,
当时我跟马云的一个好朋友,
我俩我吃饭,
因为那个女的很厉害,
我跟他吃饭,
我跟他讲,刘志军要被抓了,
他跟我说不可能啊,
我们俩在哪儿,在工体呢,吃饭,
我说已经把他的外围都打完了,
马上就到他,他还不相信,
大强迫打核心疫苗,
他是从工作角度,
他包括他家族干这些事,
他未必知道啊,
陈浩不认识,
刘志军和专门讲一期的,
刘志军跟你讲讲刘志军的故事,
刘志军和卖鸡蛋老太太的故事,
还有那个红炉剧组,
原来我在推特上说,
刘志军把那个红炉剧组那几个女演员
全部都睡了,
他们还不相信,
说你为什么都说都,
是不是有漏网之余,
我说他没有漏网之余,
秦岳飞,
打到没招了,
中国会出来调解的,
中国现在不说,
就会调解的,
对,
广西科技厅长,
那就是那个姓李嘛,
就是马彪的人嘛,
他把马彪的儿子,
给办你一笔大的,
所以就是,
马彪对他很好嘛,
你还给他弄了个正听级,
也看不错了,
从一个正处弄到,
处处弄到正听级,
胡海峰跟浙江派系关系好吗?
有传言要调动,
他有能力办事嘛,
他没有任何能力办事,
你看这个陈希给胡海峰,
他安排工作,
都是个安排的挺好,
清华空谷党委书记,
大家知道,
校旗里面比较牛的,
就是一把手,
是董事长二把手总经理,
党委书记是干啥的,
有级别,
有正处级别,
但是不让你管事,
到了那个清华大学,
那个,
清华大学那个长三教研究院,
正江厂三演员,党委书记,
你以为党委书记听得挺大吧?
但那个演员院有院长,
院长是一把手干活着,
党委书记又是那个,
所以他直接,
他真正干事就是在
浙江那几年,
所以他能干什么事?
两轮醋油的胡海峰,
所以,
而且他这个政府关系,
就这个关系,
他变成了一个符号了,
所以习一般不会动他的,
一般不会用他的,
而且不会用他的,
他既没能力,
有没有这个关系,
他现在又敏感了,
表儿子在北大,
孙心阳在海南,
他是那个习正宁,
就是习近平大哥的手下呀,
他有这个渊源,
而且跟习家,
跟那个习近平大姐关系,
都很好,
帮了办了很多事,
安排了很多事,
考虑台海行事,
为了福建和厦门的发展如何,
打吧也不会那个,
你要有房子,
我觉得谨慎,
现在看来打台湾是时间问题,
时间问题,
你不要在当地持有什么房产,
别的,
你也没有什么影响,
不要在当地制产,
为什么福建这些年,
基础社是一直很烂,
就是因为一直估计,
哪天打仗打烂了,
谢谢小易啊,
谢谢,
谢谢大少,
刘志军,
给在监视宾馆,
给江夏贵,
这个我没听说,
夏贵有些时候,
不一定是物理上的,
肉体上的夏贵,
有些时候,
可能是精神上的夏贵,
他精神上绝对夏贵了,
但是刘志军后半成,
他就已经转,
已经换大腿,
换到温那里去了,
因为他看到温,
保了很多人,
你看温家保牛逼在哪里,
我第一想查的人,
我都能查了,
第二我能保人,
你看金人庆,
财政部长,
涉及了那个,
李维公共刑,
复案,
被保了吧,
那个,
文化部长叫什么,
余佑军吧,
余佑军他觉得有财,
也给保了,
然后还有那个,
邱耀,
邱什么,
就是统计局长叫邱什么,
也是犯了男女关系,
他觉得有财,
他也给保了,
刘军,
你看我靠,
给了温家,
太好了,
能保人,
所以他给了温家保,
然后他忽略了,
胡锦涛的关系,
这个刘志军,
所以就被干了,
却要滑的,
所以这个刘志军,
就被,
当时胡锦涛,
也不知道哪儿,
抽风了,
连他身边的人,
就说,
都不知道怎么批了,
但是,
批了,
机会就得办,
像那种花般事件,
我就是特别想做一个严肃的,
你们老是逼我做不严肃的,
我以后慢慢讲点,
讲点画边的,
胡的外甥女婿,
感觉滑太这个位置,
他不是的,
你说的那个周啊,
周是这样子,
他不叫外甥女婿吧,
他的妹妹,
她姐姐,
还是妹妹的女婿,
这叫什么,
这叫直女婿吧,
周在那里没有权利,
当时因为,
当时后来没选完中央委员,
就给她找个地方,
当时时代也从她专门,
专门安抚了她一下,
周,
周一,
周什么,
她说了两句话,
很有道理,
跟我讲过两句话,
她说,
因为她是滑太证券的,
没有任何企业上不了市,
第二,
没有任何上市的企业,
没有缺点的,
这是她两个特点,
她其实也是那种典型的女婿,
没有什么,
你说能力怎么样,
也不行,
也不是特别强,
但是人吧,
还算不错,
尼姆的企业家不认识,
孙立军我会做的,
孙立军的中国政治影响很大的,
孙立军另一句话,
苗华,
三个人就看着
他的级别不高,
都是秘书,
但是他实际上掌握的权力
是非常大的,
另一句话相当于
把整个党的组织权拿到了,
苗华管的是整个
军队体系的这个人事权,
然后孙立军,
当时是管了整个
政法系统的人事权,
他们因为跟领导的
关于好奇,
都是掌握了整个
系统的人事权,
所以他们都是一个派系,
所以孙立军,
你看是个副部级,
他管着很多政部级的人,
你看,
因为他被查的那几个人,
都是各省公安厅长,
你想想中国三十多个县
有六七个公安厅长,
都是他提拔起来的,
你就想知道孙立军的影响,
孙立军扶植了很多人,
对,劉志军那是干那个郑州局,
得罪他的,真是真干,
劉志军是敢干的,
包括中国的高铁,
这个技术没有劉志军是不行的,
他采取了很多招,
一逃杀三世,
来对付国外的那些,
没有劉志军,
包括采取了很多的措施,
规避发改委那些立项,
所以没有劉志军,
是没有中国现在的高铁,
这绝对是个能人,
而且他,
你想想胡渭那十年,
胡渭十年做的好是什么,
是因为前任打下来的基础,
一个是入市,
一个是启动房地产,
都是朱镂基打下来的基础,
包括办奥运会,
也都是上一任,
就是01年就已经申请下来的,
胡渭主要干了两个什么事,
特别是温家宝,
你想想那十年,
他们俩主动干的事,
就是你想想是什么,
对后来影响深院一个四万亿,
你不管好的,
坏的是对后来影响巨大,
目前来看正面的桌,
第二个就是什么,
第二个就是高铁,
高铁就是把中国变小了,
把中国的市场变小了,
距离变近了,
北京到上海,
你看就五个小时做那个,
把整个的市场连接起来了,
把人的流动,
这些东西连接起来,
所以他整个对中国经济的发展,
对中国在很多技术上的进步,
是非常厉害的,
中国后来能拿到,
一代一六能拿出去的是啥,
那些普通的基建,
是没有啥技术海量的,
就是高铁的牛逼,
就是高铁的技术,
所以刘志军绝对能当一个副总理,
他呢也是吃亏在这里,
他就非要,
他就想当这个副总理,
你要就干个部长,
估计也没人干你,
你非想当那个国务委员,
那一堆人想阴谋你嘛,
位置毕竟太少了,
欢迎布瑞林,
权力变现,
伍列官员,
这得讲一专期,
你再能讲吧,
你看讲的,
咱们的船是正道,
教你如何和,
和政府官员打交道,
不是叫伍列官员,
那也不叫权力变现,
你这话说的太难听了,
你换一个说法,
你要像咱们共产党一样,
像毛老毛一样,
把一个事儿说得,
关面堂谎一点,
那多舒服啊,
中国现在老和流氓国家走那么,
你上面难道不知道吗?
他哪知道什么流不流氓,
听他的话,
他的立场不一样,
都知道,
哪有不知道,
他选的路不一样,
他走的路,
他知道,
他跟西方的那么一块去啊,
马星瑞的事对其他山东帮有影响吗?
没有影响,
你不要看,
因为他是山东帮有什么,
他主要是航天和新疆的事,
估计,
估计那个深圳的事,
他当一把手的地方有事,
所以跟山东帮有什么关系?
是不是?
没有另的事,
团派能另分秋色吗?
没有,
如果没有那个车祸,
另一句话不出事,
大概,
大概率中国的政治
跟我现在完全不一样,
大概能4比6吧,
或者4.5比5.5吧,
大概平分秋色哪一点,
稍弱一点,
但是也能博弈了,
跟他的身体不好没关系,
跟胡的身体不好没关系,
当然有点关系,
他关系没说的那么大,
1718年,
因为习已经当了那个,
16年他已经上位了,
16年他已经确定为核心了,
后边的时间,
你就是老胡早一年身体不好,
晚一年身体不好,
其实不影响那个了,
你在16年之前的身体不好,
还是决定因素,
所以老胡身体17年左右,
身体不好,
已经不是决定因素了,
这个判断就是对这个情况不太了解,
为什么要抓胡晓辉?
胡晓辉我已经写好了,
等我找个时间把他剪出来,
你就看到就知道了,
胡晓辉得罪了所有人,
胡晓辉是典型的,
就是不知道核,
他跟薄熙来有点像,
太嚣张了,
要忘记自己身份,
然后逗天逗地,
把所有的方面都得罪了,
你到时候看我视频吧,
就讲这些大企业家,
这些人我都打过交道,
所以我跟你讲的,
你包括讲王健林,
Twitter,
YouTube上讲那么多人,
在我之前哪有知道大马案件,
哪有知道安全部的事儿的,
哪有知道王健林,
跟那些人的这些东西的,
包括我到时候我讲那个,
许家印,
你就看我写的许家印,
什么样的许家印,
他有都是有优点,
你许家印这个人就很大气,
我到现在就,
就是,
就很佩服许家印,
这个人很大气,
他许家印的毛病在哪里呢,
太自信了,
历史上死过很多次,
都活过来了,
08年已经快要死了,
活过来了,
所以他,
许家印是没有意识到自己,
要这个很大要倒了,
他一直以为自己还有办法救,
那个直到,
直到他倒,
就是崩盘前的,
违约前的一个月,
他还去找那个,
宁高宁还找谁合作说,
合作说要搞,
要投多少,
十个亿还多少去付贫呢,
所以你看许家印,
后来是比较被动的,
就是他出事之后,
他的,
你看,
碧贵园出事,
之前,
已经把钱捐给一个信托了,
所以我给家里,
就光明正大的,
留了一百多个亿,
你也穿透不了,
许家印,
你看,
他最后是出了事之后,
在仓促的转钱,
转钱之后,
又被上市公司的公告出来了,
所以造成大家都很反感他,
然后他的儿子没跑出去,
老婆跑出去了,
找了个外国小男友,
你说,
你这个不尴尬了,
一部分钱还被动,
动结了,
所以许家印,
你想想,
他一想到自己老婆,
拿着他钱,
找了个外国小男友,
你想想那个吧,
他反不反,
谢谢剧烈,
谢谢,
对不认识,
很实在,
我知道很多人关心这个东西。
戴北方,
他主要是劉玉普,
当时提的人,
其实跟马星瑞,
他估计有点关联,
那关联不大,
戴北方是自首的,
这句话,
车祸那个儿子,
怎么逆转局面了?
对,
主要警卫局,
没上报,
包括,
隐瞒,
还栽赃给那个,
栽赃给那个,
贾庆陵的私生子,
当时我们,
一开始传,
都是,
都是那个,
贾庆陵的私生子,
和贾庆陵很生气嘛,
啊,
后来我,
我一个领导的大秘,
一个常委的大秘,
他是,
我跟他喝茶,
他说,
因为他知道,
他就问我说,
你去,
了解一下小令,
还,
还在不在,
最近脸,
脸不脸,
能不能联系到他?
啊,
当时一开始,
他说完之后,
我才意识到有问题,
王中陵,
牵手老马的案子,
这,
他俩,
巴干的打不着,
他俩认识吧,
会喝酒的关系,
都瞎说,
民生银行太大胆,
以后会讲的,
啊,
问,
问家红,
再衡大当个顾问,
西北来不及讲了,
那个谁说的,
那个车祸,
零句话儿子,
车祸对中国政治影响,
我们就说,
影响二十年到三十年,
甚至五十年,
平安的时空人到底是谁?
等我讲,
平安吧,
司机有很多种含义,
在北京搞了四套店,
那个四合院,
有没有可能是买的?
这我怎么判断的?
你看看他有没有钱,
也可能是买的,
也可能是租的,
他要买的,
这两年买的,
他就是个傻子,
都卖不出去了,
他要是租的一定好,
哦,
许家英老婆,
找外国男友是有策略,
有目的,
当然有目的,
这个年纪,
老太太有钱,
很正常,
能理解,
谢谢,
三大石油一把手,
后面的关系,
哎呀,
现在都没有原来,
那么格局那个了,
现在包括石油,
包括这些国企,
已经换得太厉害了,
所以你说,
他们都是党的人,
都是其他人,
而且他们这一个系统的,
基本上,
其实不像原来,
大家想的,
就是谁家的人,
谁家人,
那么厉害了,
张彪,
张磊和沈南盟,
他俩,
你不能说他是白手套,
他俩都是靠技术的,
他和沈南盟在一起,
都早期起,
包括张磊,
头腾性的时候,
头腾性都是京东,
京东都是,
当时都是很困难的时候,
那个时候,
你只要给钱,
刘强东都那个,
都要啊,
刘强东求着你,
08年,
你去刘强东那时候亏税呢,
我们那时候也碰到,
京东的投资机会啊,
就说,
要头头京东啊,
当时,
我们那个目光,
当时对那玩意,
当时在,
我还在那个机构里,
昨天对这玩意,
就是也收获不了我那个机构。
老许对,
对破产,
绝对没有预测,
绝对没有布局。
他布局了,
就说,
你告诉我,
他布局啥了?
他把钱转出去了,
那后来干啥了?
就转了500亿,
还被搞成这样。
评价马云,
马云在复杂了,
一句两句说不清楚,
到时候我给马云,
我写,
马云会专门讲一期的,
想想,
华为在政商关系方面,
人,
政,
非,
其他国,
人非做的是不错的,
首先去做企业,
你首先把自己的活干好,
你把活子你干成典型的,
大家都,
都会那个支持你,
包括万科早年,
他也是干的活好,
你干的活好,
那个,
然后在这方面,
当然是,
华为在北京的公关,
他也很厉害的,
华为在北京那个,
有个公关团队,
专门公关股盖好,
这些,
就一带一路出去的,
周祖义,
执政不怎么样,
又没信长信,
王浩惠舔,
进一步希望他们,
你不是看执政,
大家不要看政绩,
什么政绩,
政绩不政绩,
领导用你,
政绩都是说明,
都是加分像,
领导不用你,
你干的再好都没用,
你不要看政绩,
周祖义,
周祖义下的一些,
肯定进步,
他跟陈希这关系,
跟丁薛阳的关系,
他不是一个人,
另外他在福建,
就是你在福建,
这个省本身就说明了,
你的后备很强,
因为福建,
这个福建,
陕西这种地方,
浙江这些地方,
你想,
这种好地方,
把你放在这,
就是让你在当地,
跟上面接通关系的,
你只要别得罪太多人,
就行,
把这几个老同志搞好,
把这些大佬在当地的人,
该提拔着提拔起来,
把何立峰在当地人提起来,
蔡奇在当地的人搞起来,
陈希在当地人搞好,
他这种铁不是说,
你就是公开的说,
伟大领袖怎么样怎么样,
不是这种,
他这好多东西,
你看不到的,
廖建民,
廖建民不属,
余祖善,
余祖善一般,
他跟刘慈善,
余老习的关系,
你怎么说呢,
看不到他俩关系特别好,
我只能这么说,
你看一看,
余祖善,
余祖善后来,
就是在那当解说员了,
没有那个,
56, 57,
的司长原地提夫,
这些一般都统一申选,
当然部长推荐也很重要,
现在部委提拔,
一般比原来要强多了,好多了,
女的儿子,
余祖善儿子在哪里,
你回头发给我,
庄主,
你回头,
Telegram,
联系我一下,
我看你,
你对这些了解比较多,
可以说一下,
高校,
高校什么情况呢?
是不是,
绝大多数领导,
都是因为女人出事,
女人不是事,
在咱们党来说,
从老毛到高岗,
谁没有女朋友,
那女朋友,
这俩都是属于烂到那样的,
但都没事,
对于老毛来说,
这个都不是事,
周恩来没有女朋友吗?
邓元来也有女朋友,
谁没有女朋友,
没有女朋友少数,
咱们党,
你就看看,
上一代的年代人,
没有女朋友只有少数,
林彪没有女朋友,
陈云比较间谍,
然后还有谁,
身体不好的这几个,
别的呢,
都有女朋友,
共产党来说,
不是事,
共产主义就是,
觉得这玩意不是事,
共产共期,
不是事,
上摊,
马云这个我会讲的,
等着吧,
我专门了解过,
马云身边的人,
马云这个外摊峰会,
他是怎么,
谁讲的,
谁给他写的稿,
然后他怎么回事,
背后怎么弄,
我专门讲,
讲一下,
物业股份,
统计信托,
这个不用中央管,
碧桂园的事,
还有中央吗?
许家印,
许家印不在间谕,
监视居住,
知道吧?
许家印,
两个儿子有报道证,
大儿子报道证,
儿子关系不好,
赵薇我会讲的,
赵薇给黄有龙,
我很快就要写了,
摩爾县城和墨西,
我不了解,
高级公安的人,
什么呢?
高级公安,
你看那个,
正大的杨晓平就牛,
这就跟什么人,
就是你要,
情商要高,
会接力打利,
这个是顶级能力,
互合好道的情况吧,
30 枚背景的基层人员,
没什么,
我觉得人生啊,
我能跟大家说一下,
说一下几个人,
你觉得李白是啥级别?
李白后来是不是
连科技都没混到啊?
是不是?
很多大人物,
你觉得他很有名,
但其实他在,
你要从官场的角度,
他是很失败的,
是不是,
那个什么徐霞克,
就是个无业人员啊,
但人在别的领域,
取得了很大的发展,
所以你,
你评价这些人,
我就评价人生,
有很多维度,
不一定说,
我非要当督大官,
或者赚多少钱,
你可以在别的方面,
发展得挺好,
你可以比他们长壽,
你可以比他们,
看得更,
更开,
王,
刘强动我会讲的,
王星比较傻了吧,
记得,
王星的公关是不行的,
所以被搞过一个人,
谢之坤最大的家族,
是最大,
谢之坤家族关系,
比较多,
但是,
特别高层的他不行,
嗯,
他搞关系太粗了,
啊,
谢之坤搞关系太粗了,
所以最后,
造成了这个情况,
嗯,
高杨的子女,
何被身为自己高杨的子女,
我不太了解,
但我估计一般,
高杨的子女在深圳嘛,
后来,
啊,
当时那个,
呃,
在哪里啊?
啊,
那个不是高杨,
那个是高那个,
嗯,
是人民日报那个社长高什么,
啊,
高杨子女我不太了解,
没大听说过,
嗯,
谁知道的可以,
群里有谁知道的可以说说,
好多大收购的常委会批,
不是的,
就是因为当时,
当时收购平安,
平安那个要保健会批,
保健会自己不敢定,
嗯,
因为你牵制到这个,
几万亿的一个机构,
而且是养老机构,
这些肯定要那个,
一般的不用,
戴北方被刘一普有什么呀,
戴北方,
啊,
刘一普呢,
戴北方说,
刘一普肯定出事,
刘一普的事多了去了,
嗯,
许家印,
许家印说不说,
嗯,
这个不好说了,
啊,
许家印不一定能擅中啊,
杨小平和贺杰,
和亲王是哥们对,
嗯,
华为的公关是,
他都是一个团队,
嗯,
你当你企业,
你做到华为那个级别的时候,
我就,
我可以帮你去公关,
你得首先把企业搞到那个,
量级呀,
你搞到量级,
很多人会找你的,
你有利益关系,
你比如说,
你干到一利了,
你一年要一百个亿了,
那有些人,
贾清灵的儿子,
就会找你,
你把广告都给我吧,
那刘一普的儿子,
就会找你,
让我入点股吧,
你下半年公司,
我餐点股吧,
或者是,
小一点的灵道,
就会说,
你那个经常商,
你给我一个吧,
就有很多人会找你,
然后会有些人过来跟你讲,
哎,
我跟那个谁的领导,
关系很好,
我一块吃个饭吧,
就像那个马化腾,
你像那些马云,
你不都这么把关系搞去,
当你有那么多钱,
有那么多体量的时候,
会有很多人来送关系,
很多前客,
他要找你来变现,
所以你,
所以,
就是你只要别太傻,
什么的,
你都能搞点关系,
然后你再可以顾个团队,
你可以像马云一样,
我就请中东部的那个谁,
来给我当公关部长,
然后让他去我跑关系,
就行了,
高领,
现在规模太大了,
你要买的话,
我觉得不要买这种太大的,
反而从高领出来的这些人,
而且高领,
其实,
后来很多产品出现问题了嘛,
所以我建议,
你这种买的都要买,
比如说高领,
或者是,
洪山出来的年轻人搞的产品,
不要买这大的,
大的,
你搞,
本来水平很高,
管了三千亿,
你想要三千亿,
他只能回归平均收益率,
而且,
你想,
高领,
你长得再牛逼,
你能管,
你管三百亿的时候牛,
你管三千亿的时候牛吗?
华为是谁家?
华为是咱们党的呀!
从日本回国,
是妈咪,
妈妈,
还有老大的,
对有可能,
陈吉宁啊,
提些什么,
不爱,
他老婆对他影响大吗?
影响影响很大,
你们看,
他逛街,
他老婆逛街,
他在边上坐在那儿吧,
像你一样,
像我一样,
在央国起,
每天都想当官怎么办?
每想当官,
你就天天研究呗,
当官又不是什么难事,
你本身在国起里,
竞争人就少一遍,
你说人喜欢,
你就好好研究呗,
伟大领说,
认为自己是情况,
当然了,
他本人喜这个人,
本身他这个想法是好的,
让国家强大,
老百姓,
他对老百姓特别亲密,
你在他身边的工作人员,
他一点家都没有,
你如果你是政庭,
或者以下,
你可以随便给他开玩笑,
他对你可客气了,
你跟他,
他是个好人,
但是呢,
他这知识结构有问题,
他理解的,
国家的,
什么样的国家好,
他理解的,
跟咱理解的不一样,
他没有受过西方的教育,
没有,
没有这个完整的这个教育,
也没有这个现代的这些,
这个东西,
他的知识结构造成了这样,
但是你说他是坏人,
他不是个坏人,
我这么讲,
这将拿起人拍上蔡奇,
因为长洲那些人都好几个呀,
为什么疫情那么快看拍,
疫情是因为黄昆明写信了,
黄昆明写信,
然后蔡奇给你强推动了,
然后习本身自己也了解到这些情况了,
这回头我也会专门讲,
不是一个人搞的,
光客,
几光击我没关注,
拼多多高管打处长,
这个事儿,
我明天那个事儿再能讲一下,
不会太大的,
拼多多体谅在哪里,
体谅在那上海宝,拼多多,
不要问我驸马的事儿,
我不答驸任何驸马的事儿,
为啥不给黄昆明写那样,
我上回只不过通缩那期讲了,
曾是如何从恩师变成边缘人物都会讲的,
专门得讲一期,
习曾之决裂,
就跟你讲,
习王之决裂,
这个东西就得你非常了解,
这是习和曾的决裂,
是历史上一个近代历史,
一个比较大的一个事件,
而且比较诡异的,
因为曾是习的恩人,
没有曾可能在整个过程中,
起了70%的作用,
因为如果曾不大力运作,
或者他当时不帮习那么多,
习是不会那么顺利,
或者权力也不会那么大的,
贵州胡志峰不认识的,
张力,
必产还张力,
可以讲一讲,
有空有机会吧,
大大对老胡怎么样,
对,
他还是有感恩之心的,
疫情结束了怎么来着,
就看回放吧,
但是老陆认识民盟的人,
你要干嘛?
他为什么不给农民增加养老金,
因为他就这么多钱,
你看中国很多,
但是军费要吧,
一年1.45万亿,
还得增长,
真是明着看着的是吧,
然后你还要搞维稳吧,
一年4.1.4, 1.5万亿,
然后你还要给
非洲人民捐点钱吧,
是不是,
各方面哪儿不需要钱,
你还要给这些产业补贴吧,
你还要给你的基本盘,
这8000万公务员,
加点工资,
然后加点退休金吧,
所以他们觉得,
你还从来就是给公务员
掌工资觉得,
绝对不会给老百姓的,
好人为什么亲自指望,
亲自不守,
一直不放开,
这是两回事儿,
好人很好官,
好领袖是两个概念,
你知道吗,
好人不一定是好官,
好官不一定是好领袖,
高领和您的实在怎么立,
出动章类,
那这就复杂了,
平台,平台的风关和海南不一样,
这个次海南风关宣传的很大,
我觉得国内统一部署了,
连基本说负面了都没有,
前几年走了,
平台就没日报了,
也不一定,
因为他上海,
他是因为,
大家知道余震生之问吧,
余震生当时就是问那个,
上海为什么没有出这个平台型企业,
没有出马云,
所以上海其实后来出了,
几个二代的这个互联网平台,
几个二代的这个互联网平台企业,
拼多多,
还有这个小红书吧,
美团也在这个吧,
这年轻的这几个企业都在上海,
所以上海会保着几个企业,
只要不是中央震怒,
只要不是老大亲自说话,
上海我估计甚至,
带队去给他,
搞道歉一下吧,
增加儿子不行,
侄女有点紧急,
对,
江泽民的侄子侄女很多呀,
江泽民现在很火月,
增委能力怎么样,
增委挺讲意气的,
我这么跟你讲吧,
增委是这个二代里面,
台湾党里面最讲意气的,
你只要是你的朋友,
他觉得你是他的朋友,
他会两类插刀,
然后你是,
如果他的朋友被抓了,
增委绝对是,
是会竭尽全力去救的,
这是在这个官二代里面,
很少见的,
一般官二代都是不占,
都是出事就躲,
增委是很少的一个,
第二个增委跟你讲,
增委是能影响他老爸的,
一般你比如说,
另一句话的小儿子,
自己很嚣张,
他跟他爸说事,
他吓得了不得,
不会影响不了他的老爸,
增委呢,
他能影响他老爸,
他就这两点很牛逼,
其实增委他,
对钱什么的,
其实没有那么看重,
取得别人的信任,
进入人家的圈子,
这个就是技术活了,
技术活了,
你首先第一步,
你要对他很了解,
你要对他,
对这个人非常了解,
然后信任,
你要有办法一步一步的,
进入圈子,
你要先打外围,
然后慢慢在身中进来,
然后有人带你进入这个圈子,
你要打这个圈子的,
你看看,
有个不弱点,
你要找到,
谢正华家族,
你是环保部那个谢正华吗,
还是哪个?
跟领导相处有哪些,
竞技合计要紧,
那这个太多了,
你就把它当在你的女朋友,
想一下,
咋比女朋友的,
那个还太多了,
小宏叔是二代,
不是说官二代,
是二代互联网企业,
金黄普队,
金黄普是他后来按供的,
金黄普一开始是明天系的,
后来就转了好几道手,
好人,
这需要对好人进一个定义,
这种涉及到价值评判,
我一般不讨论,
大家觉得对就行,
因为谁说,
这种就是没有明确的标准,
我只能告诉你他身边的人,
对他的判断,
他不是个坏人,
他没有一个明确的坏人的心,
只能这么讲,
但是他别的方面就不好说了,
习业安深圳的都在博弈了,
这两个都是牵着到习愿平,
牵着到习家都比较腐,
他们都要找新的代言人,
如何去北戴河一号别,
一号别说明去个钓鱼台很容易,
钓鱼台我原来经常去吃饭,
钓鱼台去还不容易吗?
你没去过钓鱼台吗?
江丹,江丹经常去广西,
上回谁告诉我的,
那个陈刚,
广西的陈刚,
他是江丹的老公的表弟,
这个消息很可能的是真的,
因为为什么陈刚也是洋洲人,
另外,
陈刚从玻璃所
到冒出会那一步,
任命起来是非常诡异的,
刘祺跟他没有交道,
那为什么刘祺提拔他呢?
很可能是江丹去找了刘祺,
江丹找了刘祺,
所以江丹经常去广西,
你看江丹搞的,
现在搞了一个养老品吧,
搞了一个什么基金会,
搞了一个养老的一个地产,
还有一个国际学校,
他生意做的一般,
江丹也很讲义气,
当时那个谁被抓的时候,
江丹还想去救他,
李瑞刚,
李瑞刚找个机会讲一讲,
重庆啊,重庆可以,
重庆到时候我这样,
我当时讲完个人省委书记的时候,
我就重点再讲一讲,
就是每个省,
比如说重庆,
历代的这个社会书记,
历代的市领导,
这个的发展,
有咱们会员嘛,
就是这样的话,
可以持续的讲,
让大家了解大概每个地方,
但有些地方我也没那么熟,
所以大家有熟的地方,
可以跟我说一说,
我们可以把这个信息搞得更精确一点,
浙江出身的哪些人,
是蔡奇提吧,
武汉的那个书记,
白语有曾伟那么讲一些,
他也还行,
但不如曾伟那么讲一些,
他一个脚娃,
有点聪明,
他比曾伟聪明,
对,
他本性还是对的,
但是经历过文革,
没收过好好教育,
也需要啊,
就可以啊,
上周有几个月的,
其实我最理解,
对一个社会和时代的
框架的理解,
是很多人缺的,
因为我其实,
我觉得政治的了解,
只是一部分,
我对这个社会的判断,
还是比较准确的,
这个我可以跟你讲一讲,
包括你面临的这些选择,
这个女儿啊,还是她的人吗?
江丹是哪位?
江丹是江泽民的侄女,
妹妹的女儿,
这个叫侄女还是外甥女,
我现在分不清了外甥女人,
老大现在气功佛教全都不尽了,
这个信的东西,
原来信,
现在还会信,
但是估计不练了,
江丹学校叫拔萃,
拔萃回去学校,
韩定明是谁的人来的,
忘了,我都查一查,
他侄子会从政,
他侄子已经从政了,
他会按照有计划的培养,
他肯定接不了班了,
就看能培养到什么程度,
有人在A股赚了几十亿,
这不是个底层人,
A股不公平,
但是,
朝股这个事儿,
哪个市场是门槛最低的,
也是门槛最高的,
你也不用说,
非要读博士,
你只要会那个就行,
你得懂这个东西是很难的,
其实隐形门槛是很高的,
本质是认知变现的一个过程,
大家记得,
一个东西你不懂,
你偶尔靠运气赚了钱,
你早晚要凭实力给输回去,
你认知跟上了,
你早晚你会赚上这个钱,
所以一个人认知到位,
他不可能没钱了,
一个人说他认知很牛,
对这个社会了解很强,
这个是很难的,
大家知道吧,
一般上就是赶上上个时代的人,
基本上都还可以,
你只要认知判断,
财务自由,
或者是财务富裕,
基本上可以的,
我见过特医工的,
我上次不是说过吗?
威天波,
那往上去搜,
还有那个叫坤林保险的那个人,
他要见过的咱也不知道真假,
我也不信,
咱们有一回要去看王岭了,
我没去, 他们都说王岭能吸收人的那个,
你的富贵之气,
还是什么财气?
Pauli Market.
Thank you.
王岭和曹永正是一个法律更强,
目前来看,
曹永正跟你,
曹永正及时逃定了,
曹永正,
而且他人家搞得很高端,
然后赚的钱,
你看都是几十亿,
而且曹永正很早就看出了这个趋势,
你们发现后来没有曹永正的下落了,
曹永正跑到国外去了,
人家还是百一身家,
王岭最后就很惨了,
王岭的层次还是low,
他最后还是被害死了,
王岭的死亡应该不是,
不是正常死亡,
王小宏和电榨主题的,
也没说他们之间的,
我没说过他们这个主题的,
我就提了一嘴,
我也没说什么,
恒利集团,
恒利集团是那个陈建华那个公司吗?
是苏州那个陈建华公司,
那个我要专门写一句,
那个我会专门写一句,
对,恒利明是丁薛祥的人,对,
咱们这个会员中有很多高手,
所以你们加入群里面好好交流,
所以咱们这个节合员,
真是太直了, 我跟你在这说,
不仅是跟我一个人,
是跟大家这些高手们交流,
对,恒利集团是体制化的,
跟地方合作,他会集体去推,
陈建华原来到地方都是
见了一个他原来的学生,
就是恒利的选调生,
老大和义母的兄弟,
关于不错,
他们哭了嘛,
你看他姐去世的时候,
他说自己哭只有两次嘛,
一次就是他姐,
听到他姐去世的时候,
然后他们经常去给那个好,
原来那个好明珠吧,
就是习仲勋的前妻,
经常给他们上,就是上坟去,
老大要知道他包庇臣之会愤怒,
他不会知道的呀,
从国内办起来,
我也募几个基金,
我自己管我自己的,
拣救那个了,
所以大家,
我永远不会这个的,
我就做一个知识博主挺好的,
给大家分享分享,
聊一聊,
我已经过了那个,
分发突强一下创业的劲了,
你们给我打点赏,
我就喝点茶,
因为我平常赚的钱都要上交给,
上交给家里,
你们给我打点赏嘛,
上次你说断先念是谁提的,
我也不知道,
我忘了,
你问我上次的事,
我老,
李瑞刚和李同,
李同是其中之一,
李瑞刚早年还在上海,
根子还在上海,
汤大跑步进重庆,
这是什么意思?
越南前途怎么样?
越南算一个关键,
转折点,
经济上,
正常还在改革,
另外那个新上来的苏联,
还又在集权,
所以跟中国现在搞得挺活着,
不知道他这个十字路口往哪走,
他集完全之后,
不知道他往哪走,
咱们再聊五分钟,
咱们再聊五分钟就下了,
我的眼睛有点花了,
公安这种增脱周上的系统,
有能力有背景的人,
在这些人当中还要排队,
有什么接近吗?
哎呀,大家不要老想着,
接近,你会的,
你懂了,有正确的路,
那就正确的,哪有什么,
你路通了,你先想着修路,
你刚才我讲的那几个人,
前面十几年,
十几年都不动,
你修通了,把自己做的也很好,
掌握了一套跟领导相处的办法,
掌握了这个自己走仕途的这些办法,
路一旦修通了,早晚有个领导会欣赏你,
这个领导不欣赏,
你看那个谁不等了十几年吗?
有个领导欣赏他两三年,
就起来了,
你想想,
这个政治这没有几步,
你正科你自己怎么能解决吧?
付出正处,付听,正听,付步,
如果你修通了,
你看,很快就起来了,
如果你修不同,没用,
所以你不要想着走捷径,
你要想着修路,
想着自己修身,
刘亚洲,
我刘亚洲会讲的,
刘亚洲也是典型的一个,
王志安,
涉及安邦案,
在我真不清楚,
梅婷是那个谁的女朋友,
梅婷大小姐是那个
曾庆淮的女朋友,
你这个不知道吗?
我都给大家讲讲曾庆淮,
那也让我变得八卦了,
你们呀,
方威呀,
方威有现金多呀,
方威有几个特点,
第一,他的产业现金多,
在这个时候现金为王,
你现在有几个手里随着面
拿出几百亿现金的,
第二个是方威大法,
方威特别大法,
你在方威底下当职业经理人,
你那个了,
你讲没事,
现金一卡,
讲几百万,
马教授,
马教授你不知道吗?
老肖的得力干净叫,
马洪焰,
范波摄影很好,
对,
他是摄影师,
他是那个谁,
黄耀龙的表弟,
黄耀龙是孙立军的人,
关于好,
我也不能算他的人,
黄耀龙,
孙立军那是关于不错,
越南的话题,
大家都找时间聊,
但是曾经怀,
战尔巴境的这个,
梅廷是在战尔巴境,
社长和曾经怀
直接打过交道嘛,
你猜猜嘞,
许晴啊,
许晴的故事就多了,
从早期的那个,
一日千里叫王什么,
王雪冰啊,
后来王志文啊,
冯晓刚啊,
黄光玉啊,
所以许晴,
你看看他长的那样,
他是很多,
就是冯晓刚那一代人,
许晴,
原他们早年的梦想啊,
还拍了那个老炮什么的,
黄光玉他是被抓也是,
因为他在许晴他抓的,
曾经播,
曾经播不了解他有什么背景,
都是一伤心造为的心,
你这啥意思没看懂,
国内知火油管啥的,
博主有啥推荐的吗,
知火我看的少,
油管,
油管看了别的那种吧,
实证呢,
没有几个知的看,
看看别的可以,
油管讲科学的,
讲啥的,
解密的,
讲八卦的,
怎么借色,
你只能自我阉割了,
这是正常的需求,
你不用借,
是不是,
那你要,
你该克制要克制,
余志江的后代,
孙立军就够了,
孙立军当时权力很大,
一个公安系统他都能搞定,
你当时如果孙立军支持你就够了,
小米1000亿现金,
小米1000亿现金也算那个,
所以他,
小米的策略是对的嘛,
你有一个,
本身我有主业,
所以我就造车嘛,
死那么垃圾,
就是主业不赚钱,
还整天,
本身就亏着钱的,
我还同时要造手机,
造系统,造芯片,
造那个换电站,
你手底就这两个钱,
所以他的策略是错的,
赵维,
前期的两个男朋友都没有真心对的,
哎呀,
我哪知道他俩真不真心呢,
反正都帮过赵维,
所以赵维就不想再被人控制了,
赵维这个孩子,
他有第一个聪明,
第二个自主性啊,
他后来找个,
舔他的,
找个,
与其找富二代,
不如找个富一代,
他会搞关系的,
他教会他这个嘛,
协卫江,
协卫江是哪儿?
云阳的书记是吧?
协卫江不熟,
嗯,
国内有好的投资渠道好方式,
那你小心呀,
通缩实际小心投资,
投资小心,
啊,
51了,
再把问题,
大家不要新提问了,
我把现在的提问了吧,
李斌帮助大嘛,
帮助大呀,
何匪救了李斌呀,
他跟那个了,
没有何匪哪有李斌呀,
欧展公以前为什么真的,
他就是看不上他呗,
真正常而是在起的人,
虽然高定地上,
这个别问我,
算过命吗?
算过,
连元为什么成了政治高地?
连元主要是钢铁吧,
钢场的不是这个地方吧,
连元出过哪些人出了钢场的?
出过哪些人出了钢场的?
不要新提问题了,
我眼睛已经花了,
看看,
胡大官呢,
潜,
潜规则二千女明星,
当官不好潜,
比较好潜的是那个,
呃,
制片人或者导演,
导演里面主要那个副导演,
女明星有时候
还不好弄,
就是副导演,
就是行业规则,
香港,
连元啊,
连元主要是,
连元是月阳的吗?
月阳主要是那个,
主要是毛之用,
还叫毛什么呀,
就是有一个
江西的省委书记,
后来退休之后,
当全国这些副主席,
后来他退休之后,
经常回董村,
他给老江,
我关心都挺好的,
啊,
不是,
不是什么,
主要是那个老毛,
好了,
太晚了,
谢谢大上的朋友,
谢谢会员们,
大家线下多交流,
咱们空通都挺方便的,
然后那个,
如果系统不好用了,
大家还是多看看自己的VPN,
我看看自己的网络,
没家群的家家群,
大家晚啊,
Thank you.